<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tidbits on Lillian Tsai</title>
    <link>https://tslilyai.github.io/tidbits/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Tidbits on Lillian Tsai</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://tslilyai.github.io/tidbits/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Words that cheer me up</title>
      <link>https://tslilyai.github.io/tidbits/jokes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tslilyai.github.io/tidbits/jokes/</guid>
      <description>From my favorite TV show, Jeopardy Q: To live until you are very very old or to widen one&amp;rsquo;s pupils.  A: What is dilate? Q: The ant that bothers Siddhartha.  A: What is Budapest? Miscellaneous one-liners Time flies like an arrow, fruit flies like a banana. I tried to sharpen my pencil, but it was pointless. I can count to 2 3. I have a horse named Mayo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dislocated</title>
      <link>https://tslilyai.github.io/tidbits/dislocated/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tslilyai.github.io/tidbits/dislocated/</guid>
      <description>Informal studies indicate that the pain of a dislocated elbow far exceeds that of a fractured or broken arm. After the shock wears off, every small motion sends flames through your entire body. And to make it worse, there’s the nauseating churn in your stomach when you see your arm, twisted at a gruesome angle.
My own informal study this past January1, however, would beg to differ. I can’t deny that the physical pain was bad; in fact, it remains the most physically painful experience of my life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Key Algorithm</title>
      <link>https://tslilyai.github.io/tidbits/keys/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tslilyai.github.io/tidbits/keys/</guid>
      <description>I sit next to thousands of keys. Physical, shiny, golden keys, which unlock hundreds of rooms. My hands ache from the past hours of sorting these keys, meticulously hanging them on piercing hooks and carefully selecting a handful at a time to slip into opaque bags.
This was the most mind-numbing experience all summer, worse than staring at a blank wall; I could feel my brain cells shriveling up as they memorized 4-digit key codes and fruitlessly struggled to optimize a procedure that was inherently unscalable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jailed by FreeCell</title>
      <link>https://tslilyai.github.io/tidbits/freecell/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tslilyai.github.io/tidbits/freecell/</guid>
      <description>Recently, I’ve noticed two things:
 I’ve begun playing FreeCell again, but my emotional profile while playing is unrecognizable. I always tell myself that it’s enough to “try my best”, but I can’t actually figure out what “trying my best” means.  These two observations have been on my mind lately, and I believe they’re connected on a deeper level. This is my best (slightly rambling) explanation of the connection in my mind.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>